I think it will be seen that the IDF really has done everything that is humanly possible to try to safeguard innocent civilians.
It's very hard to believe that, especially on a day when one of our producers lost nine members of his family, nine members of his family who are not members of not members of the Palestinian Islamic, not members of any group, just nine people just trying to live their lives.
First of all, I extend my sorrow to him and my sympathies.
But if I saw your report correctly, and please correct me if I say something wrong, that happened in northern Gaza, in Gaza City, where a month ago we already asked all the civilians to leave.
And most of them did. If there was like 1,200,000 people there, there was only a couple of tens of thousands left.
And one has to ask, yes, they had ample opportunity to leave.
I don't know what happened. I don't have the specific circumstances.
I know there's combat going on now in the north, still between these IDF and, and, and, and, yes, and we don't want to see anyone caught up in the crossfire.
But why didn't they heed the advice and leave the area where they had?
You can't blame them.
I don't blame them.
But you can't, there's fighting in the south now.
Where, where are, I mean, I've been asking this since October 7th, where are these people supposed to go?